Guide to the Stanley Milgram Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Teaching Files, 1960-1984; Series IV
  - City University of New York
    - Experimental Social Psychology (U747)
      - General, 1972 Spring (Box 97, Folder 71)
      - Student papers and assignments, 1972 Spring (Box 97, Folder 72)
      - Student papers: "Subway" study, 1972 Spring (Box 97, Folder 73)
      - Student papers: "Subway" study, 1972 Spring (Box 97, Folder 74)
      - Student papers: "Subway" study, 1972 Spring (Box 97, Folder 75)
      - "Subway" study, 1972 Spring (Box 98, Folder 76)
      - "Subway" study: data analysis, 1972 Spring (Box 98, Folder 77)
    - Independent Psychological Research (U802), 1972 Spring (Box 98, Folder 78)
    - Advanced Social Psychology (U746), 1973 Fall (Box 98, Folder 79)
    - Advanced Social Psychology (U746): student assignments, 1973 Fall (Box 98, Folder 80)
    - Urban research Seminar (U801.19), 1973 Fall (Box 98, Folder 81)
    - Urban Research Seminar (U801.19): Mental Mapping study data, 1973 Fall (Box 98, Folder 82)
    - Authority and the Individual (U801.30), 1974 Spring (Box 98, Folder 83)
    - Authority and the Individual (U801.30): student papers and assignments, 1974 Spring (Box 98, Folder 84)
    - Authority and the Individual (U801.30): student papers and assignments, 1974 Spring (Box 98, Folder 85)
    - Experimental Social Psychology (U747), 1974 Spring (Box 98, Folder 86)
    - Experimental Social Psychology (U747): "Hand Shake" study data analysis, 1974 Spring (Box 98, Folder 87)
    - Experimental Social Psychology (U747): student papers and assignments, 1974 Spring (Box 98, Folder 88)
    - Independent Psychological Research (U802), 1974 Spring (Box 98, Folder 89)
    - Advanced Social Psychology (U746), 1974 Fall (Box 98, Folder 90)
    - Independent Psychological Research (U802), 1974 Fall (Box 98, Folder 91)
    - Urban research (U801.32), 1974 Fall (Box 98, Folder 92)
    - Experimental Social Psychology (U747)
      - General, 1975 Spring (Box 98, Folder 93)
      - "Photography" study, 1975 Spring (Box 98, Folder 94)
      - "Photography" study: student papers, 1975 Spring (Box 98, Folder 95)
      - "Telephone" study: data analysis, 1975 Spring (Box 98, Folder 96)
        See also: box 145, folder 20-21
      - "Telephone" study: student papers, 1975 Spring (Box 98, Folder 97)
    - The Individual and Authority (U801.21), 1975 Spring (Box 98, Folder 98)
    - The Individual and Authority (U801.21): student papers and assignments, 1975 Spring (Box 98, Folder 99)
    - The Individual and Authority (U801.21): student papers and assignments, 1975 Spring (Box 98, Folder 100)
    - Advanced Social Psychology (U746), 1975 Fall (Box 98, Folder 101)
    - Advanced Social Psychology (U746): student papers, 1975 Fall (Box 99, Folder 102)
    - Research in Urban Psychology (U801.32), 1975 Fall (Box 99, Folder 103)
    - Research in Urban Psychology (U801.32): student papers, 1975 Fall (Box 99, Folder 104)
    - Experimental Social Psychology (U747)
      - General, 1976 Spring (Box 99, Folder 105)
      - "Smoking" study: "Action on Smoking and Health", 1976 Spring (Box 99, Folder 106)
      - "Smoking" study: clipped articles, 1976 Spring (Box 99, Folder 107)
      - "Smoking" study: miscellaneous information, 1976 Spring (Box 99, Folder 108)
      - "Smoking" study: data analysis, 1976 Spring (Box 99, Folder 109)
      - "Smoking" study: data analysis, 1976 Spring (Box 99, Folder 110)
      - "Smoking" study: student papers, 1976 Spring (Box 99, Folder 111)
      - "Smoking" study: student papers, 1976 Spring (Box 99, Folder 112)
      - Student papers and assignments, 1976 Spring (Box 99, Folder 113)
    - Independent Psychological Research (U802), 1976 Spring (Box 99, Folder 114)
    - Psychology of Photography and Film (U801.24), 1976 Spring (Box 99, Folder 115)
    - Psychology of Photography and Film (U801.24): readings, 1976 Spring (Box 100, Folder 116)
    - Psychology of Photography and Film (U801.24): student papers and assignments, 1976 Spring (Box 100, Folder 117)
    - Advanced Social Psychology (U746), 1976 Fall (Box 100, Folder 118)
    - Advanced Social Psychology (U746): student assignments and papers, 1976 Fall (Box 100, Folder 119)
    - Doctoral Dissertation Seminar (U803), 1976 Fall (Box 100, Folder 120)
    - Experimental Social Psychology (U747), 1977 Spring (Box 100, Folder 121)
    - Experimental Social Psychology (U747): student papers, 1977 Spring (Box 100, Folder 122)
    - Urban Psychology (U801.35), 1977 Spring (Box 100, Folder 123)
    - Urban Psychology (U801.35): student papers and assignments, 1977 Spring (Box 100, Folder 124)
    - Urban Psychology (U801.35): "Pace of Life" study, 1977 Spring (Box 100, Folder 125)
    - Advanced Social Psychology (U746), 1977 Fall (Box 100, Folder 126)
    - Advanced Social Psychology (U746): student papers, 1977 Fall (Box 100, Folder 127)
    - Mass Media (U801.38), 1977 Fall (Box 100, Folder 128)
    - Mass Media (U801.38): student papers and assignments, 1977 Fall (Box 100, Folder 129)
    - Experimental Social Psychology (U747)
      - General, 1978 Spring (Box 100, Folder 130)
      - "Line Intrusion" study, 1978 Spring (Box 100, Folder 131)
      - "Line Intrusion" study: data, 1978 Spring (Box 100, Folder 132)
      - "Line Intrusion" study: data, 1978 Spring (Box 100, Folder 133)
      - "Line Intrusion" study: data, 1978 Spring (Box 101, Folder 134)
      - "Line Intrusion" study: data, 1978 Spring (Box 101, Folder 135)
      - "Line Intrusion" study: photographs, 1978 Spring
        See: CF74
      - "Line Intrusion" study: student papers, 1978 Spring (Box 101, Folder 136)
      - "Line Intrusion" study: student papers, 1978 Spring (Box 101, Folder 137)
      - "Line Intrusion" study: student papers, 1978 Spring (Box 101, Folder 138)
      - "Line Intrusion" study: student assignments, 1978 Spring (Box 101, Folder 139)
    - Urban Psychology Through Media (318.25), 1978 Spring (Box 101, Folder 140)
    - Urban Psychology Through Media (318.25): student papers and assignments, 1978 Spring (Box 101, Folder 141)
    - Advanced Social Psychology (U746), 1978 Fall (Box 101, Folder 142)
    - Urban Psychology Through Media (U801.37)
      - General, 1978 Fall (Box 101, Folder 143)
      - Equipment acquisition, 1978 Fall (Box 101, Folder 144)
      - "Kiosk" study: includes reel to reel tape, 1978 Fall (Box 102, Folder 145)
      - "Pace of Life" data: includes Super-8 film, 1978 Fall (Box 102, Folder 146)
      - "Pace of Life" study, 1978 Fall (Box 102, Folder 147)
      - Student papers, 1978 Fall (Box 102, Folder 148)
    - Experimental Social Psychology (U747)
      - General, 1979 Spring (Box 102, Folder 149)
      - "Friend Finders" and "Penny" studies, 1979 Spring (Box 102, Folder 150)
      - "Friend Finders" study: data, 1979 Spring (Box 102, Folder 151)
      - Student papers and assignments, 1979 Spring (Box 102, Folder 152)
      - Student papers and assignments, 1979 Spring (Box 102, Folder 153)
    - The Individual and Authority (U801), 1979 Spring (Box 102, Folder 154)
    - Advanced Social Psychology (U746), 1979 Fall (Box 102, Folder 155)
    - Advanced Social Psychology: student papers, 1979 Fall (Box 102, Folder 156)
    - Doctoral Dissertation Seminar (U803), 1979 Fall (Box 102, Folder 157)
    - Urban Psychology Through Film (U801.51)
      - General, 1979 Fall (Box 102, Folder 158)
      - Equipment acquisition, 1979 Fall (Box 102, Folder 159)
      - "Steam" Study, 1979 Fall (Box 102, Folder 160)
      - "Street as Marketplace" study, 1979 Fall (Box 102, Folder 161)
      - Student papers and assignments, 1979 Fall (Box 102, Folder 162)
    - Experimental Social Psychology (U747), 1980 Spring (Box 102, Folder 163)
    - Experimental Social Psychology (U747): student papers, 1980 Spring (Box 102, Folder 164)
    - Social Psychology (2475), 1980 Spring (Box 103, Folder 165)
    - Social Psychology (2475): student papers and assignments, 1980 Spring (Box 103, Folder 166)
    - Advanced Social Psychology, 1980 Fall (Box 103, Folder 167)
    - Advanced Social Psychology: student papers, 1980 Fall (Box 103, Folder 168)
    - Urban Psychology (U801.62)
      - General, 1980 Fall (Box 103, Folder 169)
      - Student papers and assignments, 1980 Fall (Box 103, Folder 170)
      - "Litter" study, 1980 Fall (Box 103, Folder 171)
      - "Litter" study: equipment, 1980 Fall (Box 103, Folder 172)
    - Experimental Social Psychology
      - General, 1981 Spring (Box 103, Folder 173)
      - "Cyranic" study: data analysis, 1981 Spring (Box 103, Folder 174)
      - "Cyranic" study: expenses, 1981 Spring (Box 103, Folder 175)
      - "Cyranic" study: student papers, 1981 Spring (Box 103, Folder 176)
      - "Cyranic" study: student papers, 1981 Spring (Box 103, Folder 177)
      - "Cyranic" study: student papers, 1981 Spring (Box 103, Folder 178)
      - Student papers, 1981 Spring (Box 103, Folder 179)
    - Film and Video as Research Tools in Social Science (U801.61) and (U801.62)
      - General, 1981 Spring (Box 103, Folder 180)
      - Student papers and assignments, 1981 Spring (Box 103, Folder 181)
      - "Old Neighborhood" study, 1981 Spring (Box 103, Folder 182)
    - Advanced Social Psychology (U746), 1981 Fall (Box 103, Folder 183)
    - Advanced Social Psychology (U746): student papers, 1981 Fall (Box 103, Folder 184)
    - Independent Research (U802), 1981 Fall (Box 103, Folder 185)
    - Dissertation Supervision (U900), 1981 Fall (Box 103, Folder 186)
    - Urban Research (U801.29)
      - General, 1981 Fall (Box 103, Folder 187)
      - "Time" study, 1981 Fall (Box 104, Folder 188)
      - "Time" study: data, 1981 Fall (Box 104, Folder 189-194)
      - "Time" study: data analysis, 1981 Fall (Box 104, Folder 195-196)
      - "Time" study: student papers, 1981 Fall (Box 104, Folder 197)
    - Experimental Social Psychology (U747), 1982 Spring (Box 104, Folder 198)
    - Experimental Social Psychology (U747): student papers and assignments, 1982 Spring (Box 104, Folder 199)
    - Advanced Social Psychology (U746), 1982 Fall (Box 104, Folder 200)
    - Advanced Social Psychology (U746): conformity lectures materials, 1982 Fall (Box 104, Folder 201)
    - Dissertation Supervision (U900), 1982 Fall (Box 104, Folder 202)
    - Independent Psychological Research (U802), 1982 Fall (Box 104, Folder 203)
    - Urban Psychology (U801.58), 1982 Fall (Box 104, Folder 204)
    - Urban Psychology (U801.58): student papers and assignments, 1982 Fall (Box 104, Folder 205)
    - Urban Psychology (U801.58): student papers and assignments, Vertical City, 1982 Fall (Box 105, Folder 206)
    - Dissertation Supervision (U900), 1983 Spring (Box 105, Folder 207)
    - Experimental Social Psychology (U747), 1983 Spring (Box 105, Folder 208)
    - Experimental Social Psychology (U747); "Social Influence" study, 1983 Spring (Box 105, Folder 209)
    - Experimental Social Psychology (U747): "Social Influence" study, data, 1983 Spring (Box 105, Folder 210)
    - The Individual and Authority (U801.30), 1983 Spring (Box 105, Folder 211)
    - Advanced Social Psychology (U746), 1983 Fall (Box 105, Folder 212)
    - Advanced Social Psychology (U746): student papers, 1983 Fall (Box 105, Folder 213)
    - Experimental Social Psychology (U747)
      - General, 1984 Spring (Box 105, Folder 214)
      - "Cyranoid" study, 1984 Spring (Box 105, Folder 215)
      - "Cyranoid" study, 1984 Spring (Box 105, Folder 216)
      - "Cyranoid" study: student papers, 1984 Spring (Box 105, Folder 217)
    - Social Psychology II (U801.26), 1984 Spring (Box 105, Folder 218)
    - Social Psychology II (U801.26): student papers, 1984 Spring (Box 105, Folder 219)
    - Advanced Social Psychology (U746), 1984 Fall (Box 105, Folder 220)
    - Urban Psychology (U801.58), 1984 Fall (Box 105, Folder 221)
    - Notes on student participation, 1968-1984 (Box 105, Folder 222-223)
    - Miscellaneous student papers, Undated (Box 105, Folder 224)
    - Unidentified audio tape of seminar, Undated (Box 106, Folder 225)
    - Unidentified audio tape for social psychology course, Undated (Box 106, Folder 226)
- Data Files, 1960-1984; Series V
  Materials in Series V, Data Files, are restricted for seventy-five years from the date of the conclusion of the experiment (2035-2060).
  Material in this series is arranged by study title in alphabetical order.
  - Cyranic
    The experiental data files are restricted until January 1, 2060.
    - Session A, 1981 (Box 107)
    - Session B, 1981 (Box 107)
    - Session C, 1981 (Box 107)
    - Session D, 1981 (Box 107)
    - Session E, 1981 (Box 107)
    - Session F, 1981 (Box 107)
    - Session G, 1981 (Box 107)
    - Session K, 1981 (Box 107)
    - Interactants, 1981 (Box 107)
    - Mediums, 1981 (Box 107)
    - Unfiled, 1981 (Box 107)
    - Pilot subjects, 1983 (Box 107)
    - Subjects, 1983-1984 (Box 107)
    - Experiment 1, 1983 (Box 107)
    - Cyranic attribution (Experiment 1): consent forms, 1984 (Box 107)
    - Cyranic attribution (Experiment 1): group I JC/DL, 1984 (Box 107)
    - Cyranic attribution (Experiment 1): group II JL/DC, 1984 (Box 107)
    - Cyranic attribution (Experiment 1): group III DL/JC, 1984 (Box 107)
    - Cyranic attribution (Experiment 1): group IV DC/JL, 1984 (Box 107)
    - Young Cyranoid: photographs, 1984 (Box 107)
    - Condition 2: subjects 201-220, 1984 (Box 107)
  - Group influence over time, 1960 (Box 108)
    The experiental data files are restricted until January 1, 2036.
  - Interocular time gap, 1969 February-March (Box 108)
    The experiental data files are restricted until January 1, 2045.
  - Mescaline
    The experiental data files are restricted until January 1, 2039.
    - Data, dart game, 1963 (Box 108)
    - Tape of Milgram after having taken drug, Circa 1963 (Box 108)
  - New York-Paris (Box 108)
    The experiental data files are restricted until January 1, 2052.
    - New York City image: correspondence with subjects, 1976, undated (Box 109)
    - New York City image: questionnaires, 1970 January 27-March 5 (Box 109)
    - New York City image: questionnaires, 1970 March 14-April 10, undated (Box 110)
    - New York City image: subjects, Circa 1970 (Box 111)
    - New York City image: subjects, Circa 1970 (Box 112)
    - Mental maps of New York City: questionnaires (1st); mental maps, 1975 November 10 (Box 113)
    - Mental maps of New York City: questionnaires (2nd), Undated (Box 114)
    - Paris: correspondence with subjects, 1973 (Box 115)
    - Paris: questionnaires, Undated (Box 115)
    - Paris: carte 1; carte 2 (for rides and walks), Undated (Box 116)
  - Norwegian-French, Undated (Box 117)
    The experiental data files are restricted until January 1, 2035.
  - Obedience, 1961-1963
    These data files are restricted until January 1, 2039.
    The Obedience experiments were conducted by Milgram between 1961 and 1963; all materials relating to this experiment were created during that time period. Specific dates of the materials are not indicated in this inventory. Researchers should note that in some conditions, a few subjects were given more than one subject number; these are noted at the file level if known.
    Some data from this study has been redacted for researcher use. Details provided at file level.
    - Data by Condition
      - Condition 00
        There are no recordings of this condition in the collection.
        - Subject files, 1961 (Box 118, Folder 1-6)
          Includes files files for Subjects 0001-0004, 0012, 0015, x0001-x0012.
      - Condition 01
        - Audiorecordings of experiments, subjects 0101, 0103-0106, 0108-0130, x0122, 5 (Box T1–T5)
        - Transcripts, breakoff, 1961 (Box 127, Folder 1)
        - Subject files, subjects 0101-0140, 1961 (Box 118, Folder 7-46)
          Subject files for subjects 31-40 also labelled x13-x22.
      - Condition 02
        - Audiorecordings of experiments, subjects 0201-0240, 6 (Box T5–T10)
          - Preservation masters
            - Unredacted, 40
            - Redacted, 40
          - Use copies (redacted)
            - Subject 0201, 1 (Box T5Ua2)
            - Subject 0202, 1 (Box T5Ub2)
            - Subject 0203, 1 (Box T5Uc2)
            - Subject 0204, 1 (Box T5Ud2)
            - Subject 0205, 1 (Box T5Ue2)
            - Subject 0206, 1 (Box T6Ua2)
            - Subject 0207, 1 (Box T6Ub2)
            - Subject 0208, 1 (Box T6Uc2)
            - Subject 0209, 1 (Box T6Ud2)
            - Subject 0210, 1 (Box T6Ue2)
            - Subject 0211, 1 (Box T6Uf2)
            - Subject 0212, 1 (Box T6Ug2)
            - Subject 0213, 1 (Box T6Uh2)
            - Subject 0214, 1 (Box T7Ua2)
            - Subject 0215, 1 (Box T7Ub2)
            - Subject 0216, 1 (Box T7Uc2)
            - Subject 0217, 1 (Box T7Ud2)
            - Subject 0218, 1 (Box T7Ue2)
            - Subject 0219, 1 (Box T7Uf2)
            - Subject 0220, 1 (Box T7Ug2)
            - Subject 0221, 1 (Box T7Uh2)
            - Subject 0222, 1 (Box T8Ua2)
            - Subject 0223, 1 (Box T8Ub2)
            - Subject 0224, 1 (Box T8Uc2)
            - Subject 0225, 1 (Box T8Ud2)
            - Subject 0226, 1 (Box T8Ue2)
            - Subject 0227, 1 (Box T8Uf2)
            - Subject 0228, 1 (Box T8Ug2)
            - Subject 0229, 1 (Box T8Uh2)
            - Subject 0230, 1 (Box T9Ua2)
            - Subject 0231, 1 (Box T9Ub2)
            - Subject 0232, 1 (Box T9Uc2)
            - Subject 0233, 1 (Box T9Ud2)
            - Subject 0234, 1 (Box T9Ue2)
            - Subject 0235, 1 (Box T9Uf2)
            - Subject 0236, 1 (Box T9Ug2)
            - Subject 0237, 1 (Box T9Uh2)
            - Subject 0238, 1 (Box T10Ua2)
            - Subject 0239, 1 (Box T10Ub2)
            - Subject 0240, 1 (Box T10Uc2)
        - Audiorecordings of breakoffs and interviews, 2 (Box 125a–125b)
          - Transcripts, 1961 (Box 127, Folder 2-3)
        - Subject files, subjects 0201-0240, 1961 (Box 118, Folder 47-86)
          - Redacted (Box 156, Folder 1-40)
      - Condition 03
        - Audiorecordings of experiments, subjects 0301-0336, x0301 (0337), x0302 (0338), x0303 (0339), x0304, x0305 (0340), 6 (Box T10–T15)
          - Preservation masters
            - Analog, subjects 0301-0336, x0301 (0337), x0302 (0338), x0303 (0339), x0304, x0305 (0340), 41 (Box T10Pd1–T10Ph1, Box T11Pa1–T11Ph1, Box T12Pa1–T12Ph1, Box T13Pa1–T13Ph1, Box T14Pa1–T14Ph1, Box T15Pa1–T15Pd1)
            - Digital (redacted)
          - Duplicating Masters
            - Unredacted, subjects 031-0336, x0301 (0337), x0302 (0338), x0303 (0339), x0305 (0340), 40 (Box T10Dd1–T10Dh1, Box T11Da1–T11Dh1, Box T11Dd2, Box T12Da1–T12Dh1, Box T13Da1–T13Dh1, Box T14Da1–T14Dh1, Box T15Da1–T15Dd1)
            - Redacted, subjects 031-033,035-0336, x0301 (0337), x0302 (0338), x0303 (0339), x0304, x0305 (0340), 40 (Box T10Dd2–T10Dh2, Box T11Da2–T11Dh2, Box T12Da2–T12Dh2, Box T13Da2–T13Dh2, Box T14Da2–T14Dh2, Box T15Da2–T15Dd2)
          - Use copies (redacted)
            - Subject 0301, 1 (Box T11Ua2)
            - Subject 0302, 1 (Box T11Ub2)
            - Subject 0303, 1 (Box T11Uc2)
            - Subject 0305, 1 (Box T11Ue2)
            - Subject 0306, 1 (Box T11Uf2)
            - Subject 0307, 1 (Box T11Ug2)
            - Subject 0308, 1 (Box T11Uh2)
            - Subject 0309, 1 (Box T12Ua2)
            - Subject 0310, 1 (Box T12Ub2)
            - Subject 0311, 1 (Box T12Uc2)
            - Subject 0312, 1 (Box T12Ud2)
            - Subject 0313, 1 (Box T12Ue2)
            - Subject 0314, 1 (Box T12Uf2)
            - Subject 0315, 1 (Box T12Ug2)
            - Subject 0316, 1 (Box T12Uh2)
            - Subject 0317, 1 (Box T13Ua2)
            - Subject 0318, 1 (Box T13Ub2)
            - Subject 0319, 1 (Box T13Uc2)
            - Subject 0320, 1 (Box T13Ud2)
            - Subject 0321, 1 (Box T13Ue2)
            - Subject 0322, 1 (Box T13Uf2)
            - Subject 0323, 1 (Box T13Ug2)
            - Subject 0324, 1 (Box T13Uh2)
            - Subject 0325, 1 (Box T14Ua2)
            - Subject 0326, 1 (Box T14Ub2)
            - Subject 0327, 1 (Box T14Uc2)
            - Subject 0328, 1 (Box T14Ud2)
            - Subject 0329, 1 (Box T14Ue2)
            - Subject 0330, 1 (Box T14Uf2)
            - Subject 0331, 1 (Box T14Ug2)
            - Subject 0332, 1 (Box T14Uh2)
            - Subject x0304, 1 (Box T10Ug2)
        - Audiorecordings of breakoffs and interviews, 2 (Box 125b–125c)
          - Transcripts, 1961 (Box 127, Folder 4-5)
        - Subject files, subjects 0301-0303, 0305-0336, x0301-x0305, 1961 (Box 118, Folder 87-126)
          Subject file x04 also labled subject 04.
          - Redacted (Box 154, Folder 1-40)
      - Condition 04
        Subject files 01-05 also labled as x01-x05.
        - Audiorecordings of experiments, subjects 0406-0427, 0436-0440, x0401 (0401), x0402 (0402), x0403 (0403), x0404 (0404), 5 (Box T15–T19)
        - Audiorecordings of breakoffs and interviews, 2 (Box 125c–125d)
          - Transcripts, 1961 (Box 127, Folder 6-7)
        - Subject files, unredacted, subjects 0406-0440, x0401-x0405, 1961 (Box 118, Folder 127-166)
      - Condition 05, Subject files, unredacted, subjects 0501-0540, 0501a-0502a, x0501-x0505, 1961 (Box 119, Folder 1-47)
      - Condition 06, Subject files, unredacted, subjects, x0601, 0601-0640 (Box 119, Folder 48-88)
      - Condition 07
        - Audiorecordings of experiments, subjects 0706-0707, 0710-0739, 4 (Box T20–T23)
        - Audiorecordings of breakoffs and interviews, 1 (Box 125d)
          - Transcripts, 1961 (Box 127, Folder 8-9)
        - Subject files, unredacted, subjects, 0701-0740, x0701-x0703, x0705 (Box 119, Folder 89-129)
      - Condition 08
        - Audiorecordings of experiments, subjects 0805-0813, 0841-0843, x0801-x0830, 7 (Box T20, Box T23–T27, Box T29)
        - Audiorecordings of breakoffs and interviews, 1 (Box 125d)
          - Transcripts (Box 127, Folder 10-11)
        - "Missing tape" (Box 119, Folder 172)
          The box is labeled "Missing," condition 08, subjects 33-36 and condition 09, subjects 17, 19-24.
        - Subject files, unredacted, subjects 0802, 0806-0841, 0843, x0801, x0803-x0805, 1961 (Box 119, Folder 130-171)
      - Condition 09
        - Audiorecordings of experiments, subjects 0901-0905, 0907-0916, 0925-0930, 0932-0939, x0901-x0905, 4 (Box T26–T27, Box T29–T30)
        - Audiorecordings of breakoffs and interviews, 2 (Box 125d–125e)
          - Transcripts, 1961 (Box 127, Folder 12-13)
        - "Missing tape"
        - Subject files, unredacted, subjects 0900-0940, x0901-x0904, 1961 (Box 120, Folder 1-45)
      - Condition 10
        - Audiorecordings of experiments, subjects 1001-1017, x1001-x1003, x1005, 5 (Box T30–T33, Box T35)
        - Audiorecordings of breakoffs, 1 (Box 125e)
          - Transcripts, 1961 (Box 127, Folder 14)
        - Subject files, unredacted, subjects 1001-1020, x1001-x1002, 1961 (Box 120, Folder 46-67)
      - Condition 11
        - Audiorecordings of experiments, subjects 1101-1135, x1102-x1105, 7 (Box T30–T36)
        - Audiorecordings of interviews, 1 (Box 125e)
          - Transcripts, 1961 (Box 127, Folder 15)
        - Subject files, unredacted, subjects 1101-1140, 1961 (Box 120, Folder 68-107)
      - Condition 12
        - Audiorecordings of experiments, subjects 1201-1215, 1217-1220, x1201-x1202, x1204, 5 (Box T35–T39)
        - Audiorecordings of breakoffs and interviews [?], 1 (Box 125e)
          - Transcripts, 1961 (Box 127, Folder 16)
        - Subject files, unredacted, subjects 1201-1220, x1201-x1204, 1961 (Box 120, Folder 108-131)
      - Condition 13
        - Audiorecordings of experiments, subjects 1301-1335, x1301-x1305, 5 (Box T36–T40)
        - Audiorecordings of breakoffs, 2 (Box 125e–125f)
          It is unclear if there are any recordings in 125e of condition 13. Box 125f begins with Condition 13, subject 33.